[
  {
    "question": "This is associated with a specific business function e.g., in a university, student registration.",
    "choices": [
      "Business Services",
      "Coordination Services",
      "Utility Services"
    ],
    "answer": "Business Services"
  },
  {
    "question": "It support composite processes such as ordering.",
    "choices": [
      "Business Services",
      "Coordination Services",
      "Utility Services"
    ],
    "answer": "Coordination Services"
  },
  {
    "question": "Those associated with some activity.",
    "choices": [
      "Task-oriented Services",
      "Utility or business Services",
      "Entity-oriented Services"
    ],
    "answer": "Task-oriented Services"
  },
  {
    "question": "In inter-organisational systems, not separate workflows are created for each organisation and linked through message exchange.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Graphical workflow notations, such as BPMN, are more readable and WS-BPEL cannot be generated from them.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The non-functional behavior of the service is predictable because it depends on load.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "If services have to be paid for as used, testing a service may be expensive.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It may be easy to invoke compensating actions in external services as these may rely on the failure of other services which cannot be simulated.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coordination Services that not support composite processes such as ordering.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "That implement general functionality used by different business processes.",
    "choices": [
      "Coordination Services",
      "Utility Services",
      "Business Services"
    ],
    "answer": "Utility Services"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Project Planning?",
    "choices": [
      "has to plan who will work on the project, how the project will be broken down into increments, how resources will be allocated across your company, etc.",
      "involves breaking down the work into parts and assign these to project team members, anticipate problems that might arise and prepare tentative solutions to those problems.",
      "when you modify your plan in the light of experience gained and information from monitoring the progress of the work."
    ],
    "answer": "involves breaking down the work into parts and assign these to project team members, anticipate problems that might arise and prepare tentative solutions to those problems."
  },
  {
    "question": "It looks ahead for several months and decides on the features that should be included in a release of a system.",
    "choices": [
      "Validation Planning",
      "Release Planning",
      "Iteration Planning"
    ],
    "answer": "Release Planning"
  },
  {
    "question": "In this approach, a formulaic approach is used to compute the project effort based on estimates of product attributes, such as size, and process characteristics, such as experience of staff involved.",
    "choices": [
      "Experience-based techniques",
      "Story-based planning",
      "Algorithmic cost modeling"
    ],
    "answer": "Algorithmic cost modeling"
  },
  {
    "question": "AT is the percentage of code automatically generated.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "ET is the percentage of code automatically generated.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "ATPROD is the productivity of engineers in integrating this code.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "ETPROD is the productivity of engineers in integrating this code.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "EAM is the adaptation adjustment multiplier computed from the costs of changing the reused code.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Estimate of equivalent number of lines of new code computed using the reuse model.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are points in the schedule against which you can assess progress.",
    "choices": [
      "Milestones",
      "Quality plan",
      "Deliverables"
    ],
    "answer": "Milestones"
  },
  {
    "question": "This services may be entity- or task-oriented, coordination services are always task-oriented.",
    "choices": [
      "Utility or business Services",
      "Task-oriented Services",
      "Entity-oriented Services"
    ],
    "answer": "Utility or business Services"
  },
  {
    "question": "Starts with the service requirements and defines the operation names and parameters associated with the service.",
    "choices": [
      "Logical interface design",
      "WSDL description",
      "Message design"
    ],
    "answer": "Logical interface design"
  },
  {
    "question": "The logical specification is converted to a WSDL description",
    "choices": [
      "Logical interface design",
      "WSDL description",
      "Message design"
    ],
    "answer": "WSDL description"
  },
  {
    "question": "During this stage of the process, you search service registries or catalogs to discover what services exist, who provides these services and the details of the service provision.",
    "choices": [
      "Select possible services",
      "Discover services",
      "Formulate outline workflow"
    ],
    "answer": "Discover services"
  },
  {
    "question": "A standard for workflow languages used to define service composition",
    "choices": [
      "WS-BPEL",
      "WSDL (Web Service Definition Language)",
      "SOAP"
    ],
    "answer": "WS-BPEL"
  },
  {
    "question": "If services have to be paid for as used, testing a service may be not expensive.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where you design the logical and WSDL service interfaces.",
    "choices": [
      "Service implementation and deployment",
      "Service candidate identification",
      "Service design"
    ],
    "answer": "Service design"
  },
  {
    "question": "The most commonly used representation for project schedules.",
    "choices": [
      "validation plan",
      "graphical Notation",
      "bar chart"
    ],
    "answer": "bar chart"
  },
  {
    "question": "ASLOC is the number of lines of generated code.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not estimate of equivalent number of lines of new code computed using the reuse model.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "A company takes on a project in a new domain. The client has not defined the process to be used and has not allowed time for risk analysis. The company has a CMM level 2 rating.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Personnel attributes Multipliers that take the experience and capabilities of the people working on the project into account.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Project attributes Concerned with the particular characteristics of the hardware development project.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The time required is not independent of the number of people working on the project.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Web Services?",
    "choices": [
      "Standard protocols have been developed to support service communication and information exchange",
      "an instance of a more general notion of a service",
      "may execute on different computers from different service providers"
    ],
    "answer": "an instance of a more general notion of a service"
  },
  {
    "question": "In this initial stage of service design, you use the requirements for the composite service as a basis for creating an ‘ideal’ service design.",
    "choices": [
      "Formulate outline workflow",
      "Discover services",
      "Select possible services"
    ],
    "answer": "Formulate outline workflow"
  },
  {
    "question": "This standard allows a service interface and its bindings to be defined",
    "choices": [
      "WS-BPEL",
      "SOAP",
      "This standard allows a service interface and its bindings to be defined"
    ],
    "answer": "This standard allows a service interface and its bindings to be defined"
  },
  {
    "question": "WS-BPEL is an XML-standard for over workflow specification.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "External services may not have modified by the service provider thus invalidating tests which have been completed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "WSDL description The logical specification is not converted to a WSDL description.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where you identify possible services that might be implemented and define the service requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "Service implementation and deployment",
      "Service candidate identification",
      "Service design"
    ],
    "answer": "Service candidate identification"
  },
  {
    "question": "PM = (ASLOC * AT/100)/ATPROD.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "ASLOC is the not number of lines of generated code.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "ESLOC = ASLOC * (1-AT/100) * AAM.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "AAM is the adaptation adjustment multiplier computed from the costs of changing the reused code.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Product attributes Concerned with required characteristics of the software product being developed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Describes the quality procedures and standards that will be used in a project.",
    "choices": [
      "Quality plan",
      "Configuration management plan",
      "Validation plan"
    ],
    "answer": "Quality plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Project attributes Concerned with the particular characteristics of the software development project.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Your selection criteria will obviously include the functionality of the services offered. They may also include the cost of the services and the quality of service (responsiveness, availability, etc.) offered.",
    "choices": [
      "Discover services",
      "Select possible services",
      "Formulate outline workflow"
    ],
    "answer": "Select possible services"
  },
  {
    "question": "Test completed service or application the process of testing the completed, composite service is more complex than component testing in situations where internal services are used.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "WS-BPEL is an XML-standard for workflow specification.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where you implement and test the service and make it available for use.",
    "choices": [
      "Service candidate identification",
      "Service implementation and deployment",
      "Service design"
    ],
    "answer": "Service implementation and deployment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Used when software is composed from existing parts.",
    "choices": [
      "Application composition model",
      "Reuse model",
      "Early design model"
    ],
    "answer": "Application composition model"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is where code is modified a size estimate equivalent to the number of lines of new source code is computed.",
    "choices": [
      "White-box",
      "Green-box",
      "Black-box"
    ],
    "answer": "White-box"
  },
  {
    "question": "Estimates are made to discover the cost, to the developer, of producing a software system.",
    "choices": [
      "Project Planning",
      "Software Pricing",
      "project startup"
    ],
    "answer": "Software Pricing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Product attributes Concerned with required characteristics of the software product being not developed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "The time required is independent of the number of people working on the project.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  }
]